<index>

  <purpose>
  This file is the entry point.
  Read this file before any coding.
  Reply in the user's language.
  </purpose>

  <execution_constraint>
  The assistant must NOT run frontend or backend systems.
  The assistant cannot execute the application.
  The user is responsible for running and testing.
  The assistant only provides reasoning, analysis, and instructions.
  </execution_constraint>

  <step1>
  Do NOT write code.
  First, read the review XML files in the same folder.
  </step1>

  <step2>
After context analysis:

1. Interpret the user request.
2. Restate it briefly.
3. Ask for confirmation.

No code allowed in this step.
If not confirmed, do not continue.
  </step2>

  <step2_bug>
If the user request is "fix a bug" (debug / error / crash / wrong behavior):

1. Load "bug_deep_thinking_rules.xml" in this folder.
2. Follow it to think deeply about root cause and repro reasoning.
3. Provide structured analysis and user-run verification steps.
4. Do NOT claim reproduction unless user confirms.
5. Do NOT write code yet.

If this XML is not read, do not continue to next steps.
  </step2_bug>

  <step2_design>
If the user request is "design a feature" (logic design / creative functionality / solution design / system design):

1. Load "creative_logic_design_rules.xml" in this folder.
2. Follow it to think deeply about product logic, edge cases, and feasibility.
3. Output a structured design proposal and ask for confirmation.
4. Do NOT write code yet.

Important:
- This is NOT UI design.
- This is logic design only (flows, rules, data, APIs, states).
If this XML is not read, do not continue to next steps.
  </step2_design>

  <step3>
Only after user confirmation (and special rules read if needed):

1. Load "context_retrieval_rules.xml".
2. Follow its search strategy.
3. Identify relevant files and code.

Do not generate new code before search is done.
  </step3>

  <step4>
Before writing any code:

1. Load "code_writing_rules.xml" in this folder.
2. Follow its coding rules strictly (style, naming, structure, patterns).
3. Only then start implementing.

If this XML is not read, do not write code.
  </step4>

  <rule>
  If review XML is not read, do not generate code.
  </rule>

  <rule>
  The assistant must NOT simulate running frontend or backend.
  Never claim the system was executed.
  Provide instructions for the user to run and report results.
  </rule>

  <rule>
  Always reply in the user's language.
  If the user uses Chinese, reply in Chinese.
  If the user uses English, reply in English.
  Do not switch language unless the user asks.
  </rule>

</index>
